{
    "id": "7e73eff13be6449e88ad2716a0fb8fb6",
    "title": "Participles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "We could not agree on any of the ………………………..",
            "description": "Participles are often used after nouns to define the nouns. This usage is similar to that of identifying relative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "discussed problems",
                "problems discussed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The ……………………………… gave their own versions of the story.",
            "description": "Participles are often used after nouns to define the nouns. This usage is similar to that of identifying relative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "people questioned",
                "questioned people"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I ate the only ………………………",
            "description": "Participles are often used after nouns to define the nouns. This usage is similar to that of identifying relative clauses.",
            "answers": [
                "left apple",
                "apple left"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am very ……………………… in the subjects you write about.",
            "description": "The past participle is used to say how people feel.",
            "answers": [
                "interested",
                "interesting"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a ………………………. ordeal.",
            "description": "The present participle is used to discuss the people or things that cause the feelings.",
            "answers": [
                "terrified",
                "terrifying"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has always been terribly frightened …………………………… dying.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He is excited ………………………….. the possibility of becoming the new CEO.",
            "description": "We say excited about.",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "about"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I don’t know why she is annoyed ………………………… me.",
            "description": "We become annoyed with people",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I was annoyed ………………………… the way she conducted herself.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "by"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "I was surprised …………………………. his attitude",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "by",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Not ……………………. what to do, I called the doctor.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "known",
                "knowing"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}